A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Administration, Program and Policy, RG 3 FA112
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, Program and Policy, 2
  - Humanities, 1958-1985; 911; 13 document cases
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1974-1990; 911.E; 41 document cases
      - Jordan, William Chester, 1981-1984, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 227)
      - Juergens, George, 1980-1983 (Box 33, Folder 228)
      - July, Robert W., 1979-1982 (Box 33, Folder 229)
      - Justman, Stewart, 1978-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 230)
      - Kaes, Anton, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 231)
      - Kaplan, Harold, 1980-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 232)
      - Kaplan, Temma, 1981-1985 (Box 33, Folder 233)
      - Kasson, John Franklin, 1979-1983, 1985, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 234)
      - Keddie, Nikki, 1979-1982 (Box 33, Folder 235)
      - Kekes, John, 1979-1983 (Box 33, Folder 236)
      - Kern, Stephen, 1976-1979 (Box 34, Folder 237)
      - Kesselman, Mark, 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 238)
      - Khim, Jhitsa (Box 34, Folder 239)
        Missing
      - Kidwell, Clara S., 1976-1979 (Box 34, Folder 240)
      - King, Bruce, 1976-1981 (Box 34, Folder 241)
      - Knoepflmacher, Ulrich C., 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 242)
      - Kolodny, Annette, 1977-1979, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 243)
      - Kommers, Donald P., 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 244)
      - Koonz, Claudia A., 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 245)
      - Kramer, Mark, 1975-1980 (Box 35, Folder 246)
      - Kriegel, Leonard, 1974-1979 (Box 35, Folder 247)
      - Krieger, Murray, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 248)
      - Kuhn, James Wesley, 1974-1979 (Box 35, Folder 249)
      - Kuklick, Bruce, 1980-1984 (Box 35, Folder 250)
      - Kurzweil, Edith, 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 251)
      - Kutler, Stanley I., 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 252)
      - Ladd, Everett Carll, Jr., 1975-1979 (Box 36, Folder 253)
      - Ladd, Everett Carll, Jr. - Supplementary Material, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 254)
      - Ladd, Everett Carll, Jr. - Supplementary Material, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 255)
      - Lahav, Pnina, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 256)
      - Lamb, Karl A., 1975-1976, 1978-1981 (Box 36, Folder 257)
      - Lamont, Rosette C., 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 258)
      - Lapidus, Gail W., 1978-1981 (Box 36, Folder 259)
      - Laqueur, Thomas Walter, 1982-1985 (Box 37, Folder 260)
      - Lauren, Paul Gordon, 1978-1981, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 261)
      - LeMahieu, Dan Lloyd, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 262)
      - Lenzer, Gertrud, 1976-1980, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 263)
      - Lesnick, Howard, 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 264)
      - Levine, George, 1981-1984 (Box 37, Folder 265)
      - Levitt, Leonard, 1980-1983 (Box 37, Folder 266)
      - Levy, David W., 1979-1982 (Box 37, Folder 267)
      - Lewy, Guenter, 1975-1980 (Box 37, Folder 268)
      - Liehm, Mira, 1977-1981 (Box 38, Folder 269)
      - Litwack, Leon F., 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 270)
      - Loewenheim, Francis L., 1976-1980 (Box 38, Folder 271)
      - Lovejoy, David S., 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 272)
      - Luckert, Karl W., 1976-1979 (Box 38, Folder 273)
      - McDonald, John J., 1977-1980 (Box 38, Folder 274)
      - McNeil, William H., 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 275)
      - McNeil, William H. - Supplementary Material - "Dilemmas of Modernization in Greece", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 276)
      - Mackay, Alfred, 1980-1984 (Box 39, Folder 277)
      - Malia, Martin, 1980-1984 (Box 39, Folder 278)
      - Mandelbaum, Michael, 1975-1980 (Box 39, Folder 279)
      - Mansbridge, Jane J., 1981-1984 (Box 39, Folder 280)
      - Mansbridge, Jane J. - Supplementary Material - "Why We Lost the ERA", 1984 (Box 39, Folder 281)
      - Marchand, C. Roland, 1978-1981, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 282)
      - Marcus, Stephen, 1979-1983 (Box 39, Folder 283)
      - Martin, Joy, 1974-1977, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 284)
      - Martin, Rex, 1982-1984 (Box 39, Folder 285)
      - Martin, Rex - Supplementary Material - Pre-grant Articles (Box 39, Folder 286)
      - Marx, Leo, 1982-1984 (Box 40, Folder 287)
      - Meisner, Maurice J., 1982-1985 (Box 40, Folder 288)
      - Meister, Robert, 1977-1983 (Box 40, Folder 289)
      - Meirs, Suzanne, 1979-1982 (Box 40, Folder 290)
      - Miller, Jean Baker, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 291)
      - Miller, Mark C., 1982-1985 (Box 40, Folder 292)
      - Miller, Richard W., 1978-1981 (Box 40, Folder 293)
      - Mills, Nicholas, 1977-1980 (Box 40, Folder 294)
      - Mintz, Sidney W., 1981-1984 (Box 41, Folder 295)
      - Molesworth, Charles, 1981-1983 (Box 41, Folder 296)
      - Moline, Jon, 1974-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 297)
      - Moore, Robert Lawrence, 1978-1981, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 298)
      - Morawski, Jill G., 1982-1986 (Box 41, Folder 299)
      - Moskos, Charles C., 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 300)
      - Nardin, Terry, 1977-1981 (Box 41, Folder 301)
      - Nathans, Sydney, 1979-1982 (Box 41, Folder 302)
      - Needleman, Jacob, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 303)
      - Nelson, John S., 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 304)
      - Neu, Jerome, 1977-1980 (Box 42, Folder 305)
      - Nickel, James W., 1980-1982 (Box 42, Folder 306)
      - Norgren, Jill, 1979-1982 (Box 42, Folder 307)
      - Nozick, Robert, 1978-1982, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 308)
      - O'Connell, Barry, 1977-1981 (Box 42, Folder 309)
      - Ocko, Jonathon K., 1982-1984 (Box 42, Folder 310)
      - Ohmann, Richard, 1981-1984 (Box 42, Folder 311)
      - Ojo-Ade, Femi, 1980-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 312)
      - Ostricker, Alicia, 1980-1984 (Box 43, Folder 313)
      - Pagels, Elaine, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 314)
      - Paletz, David L., 1975-1980 (Box 43, Folder 315)
      - Parker, Richard Barron, 1974-1975, 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 316)
      - Pattison, Robert, 1979-1982 (Box 43, Folder 317)
      - Paxton, Robert Owen, 1977-1980, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 318)
      - Pells, Richard H., 1974-1974, 1977-1980, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 319)
      - Perdue, Theda, 1979-1982 (Box 43, Folder 320)
      - Pells, Richard H. - Supplementary Material, 1985 (Box 043A, Folder 0319a)
      - Pells, Richard H. - Supplementary Material, 1985 (Box 043A, Folder 0319a)
      - Rampersad, Arnold, 1979-1980. 1982 (Box 44, Folder 321)
      - Roberge, Paul Timothy, 1981-1984 (Box 44, Folder 322)
      - Roberts, David D., 1982-1985 (Box 44, Folder 323)
      - Robinson, Lillian S., 1976-1977, 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 324)
      - Roff, William Robert, 1981-1984 (Box 44, Folder 325)
      - Rollins, Jack D., 1982-1985 (Box 44, Folder 326)
      - Rosen, Ruth E., 1977-1980, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 327)
      - Rosenberg, Charles E., 1975-1980 (Box 44, Folder 328)
      - Rosenkrantz, Barbara Gutman, 1978-1981 (Box 44, Folder 329)
      - Rosenthal, Michael, 1977-1981, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 330)
      - Ross, Stephen David, 1974-1981, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 331)
      - Rowe, John Carlos, 1981-1984 (Box 45, Folder 332)
      - Rowell, Charles H., 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 333)
      - Ruderman, Florence A., 1974-1977, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 334)
      - Rule, James B., 1976-1979 (Box 45, Folder 335)
      - Russo, John Paul, 1976-1980 (Box 45, Folder 336)
      - Ryan, Mary P., 1974-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 337)
      - Sanders, Thomas G., 1978-1982 (Box 45, Folder 338)
      - Scheiber, Harry N., 1978-1982 (Box 46, Folder 339)
      - Scheub, Harold, 1974-1976, 1978, 1980, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 340)
      - Scheub, Harold - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 341)
      - Schrock, Thomas S., 1975-1981 (Box 46, Folder 342)
      - Schudson, Michael S., 1978-1981, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 343)
      - Schultz, Stanley K., 1980-1984 (Box 46, Folder 344)
      - Sheehan, Neil M., 1974-1977, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 345)
      - Shephard, Paul, 1976-1980, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 346)
      - Shepard, William C., 1974-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 347)
      - Sherry, Michael S., 1982-1984 (Box 47, Folder 348)
      - Sherwin, Martin J., 1977-1980 (Box 47, Folder 349)
      - Showalfer, Elaine, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 350)
      - Simon, Robert L., 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 351)
      - Singer, Milton B., 1977-1980 (Box 47, Folder 352)
      - Sklar, Kathryn Kish, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 353)
      - Sklar, Robert, 1974-1977, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 354)
      - Slotkin, Richard S., 1976-1980 (Box 47, Folder 355)
      - Smith, Barbara Herrnstein, 1980-1984 (Box 48, Folder 356)
      - Smith, Rogers M., 1981-1984 (Box 48, Folder 357)
      - Smith-Rosenberg, Carroll, 1979-1983 (Box 48, Folder 358)
      - Solomon, Pearl Chesler, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 359)
      - Spitz, David, 1977-1980 (Box 48, Folder 360)
      - Spargens, Thomas A., 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 361)
      - Stack, Carol B., 1982-1985 (Box 48, Folder 362)
      - Stack, Carol B. - Supplementary Material - All Our Kin, Holding On to the Land and the Lord, 1975, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 363)
      - Stage, Sarah, 1977-1980 (Box 49, Folder 364)
      - Steiner, Peter, 1981-1984 (Box 49, Folder 365)
      - Stevens, Rosemary A., 1982-1985 (Box 49, Folder 366)
      - Stimpson, Catherine R., 1982-1984 (Box 49, Folder 367)
      - Szwed, John F., 1974-1977, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 368)
      - Tannen, Deborah F., 1981-1984, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 369)
      - Taubamn, William, 1981-1984 (Box 49, Folder 370)
      - Taylor, William R., 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 371)
      - Terrill, Thomas E., 1978-1981, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 372)
      - Trachtenberg, Alan, 1982-1986 (Box 49, Folder 373)
      - Thaxton, Ralph, 1980-1984 (Box 50, Folder 374)
      - Thorburn, David, 1976-1979 (Box 50, Folder 375)
      - Tucker, Robert C., 1981-1984 (Box 50, Folder 376)
      - Turkle, Sherry, 1979-1985 (Box 50, Folder 377)
      - Turner, Henry Ashby, Jr., 1978-1982, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 378)
      - Tushnet, Mark V., 1978-1980 (Box 50, Folder 379)
      - Unger, Irwin, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 380)
      - Unger, Roberto M., 1976-1980, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 381)
      - Unger, Roberto M. - Supplementary Material, 4/4/80 (Box 50, Folder 382)
      - Unger, Roberto M. - Supplementary Material - "Politics", 1983 (Box 51, Folder 383)
      - Unger, Roberto M. - Supplementary Material - "Politics", 1983 (Box 51, Folder 384)
      - Unger, Roberto M. - Supplementary Material - "Politics", 1983 (Box 51, Folder 385)
      - Van Voris, William H., 1976-1980 (Box 51, Folder 386)
      - Vree, Dale A., 1974-1975, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 387)
      - Wachs, Martin, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 388)
      - Walker, Lou Ann, 1982-1984 (Box 52, Folder 389)
      - Walker, Lou Ann - Supplementary Material - Hidden Signs, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 390)
      - Walters, Ronald G., 1976-1979 (Box 52, Folder 391)
      - Walton, Kendall L., 1981-1984 (Box 52, Folder 392)
      - Warner, Sam Bass, Jr., 1976-1979, 1984-1985 (Box 52, Folder 393)
      - Wax, Rosalie, 1980-1983 (Box 52, Folder 394)
      - Weber, William A., 1982-1985 (Box 53, Folder 395)
      - Weinstein, Michael A., 1974-1978 (Box 53, Folder 396)
      - White, Richard, 1980-1985 (Box 53, Folder 397)
      - Wiarda, Howard J., 1980-1984 (Box 53, Folder 398)
      - Wiarda, Howard J. - Supplementary Material - Politics and Social Change in Latin America - Human Rights and U. S. Human Rights Policy, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 399)
      - Wiener, Jonathan M., 1977-1980 (Box 53, Folder 400)
      - Williams, Loretta J., 1979-1982 (Box 53, Folder 401)
      - Windt, Peter Y., 1974-1977, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 402)
      - Wright, Susan Presswood, 1978-1981 (Box 54, Folder 403)
      - Yans-McLaughlin, Virginia, 1976-1980 (Box 54, Folder 404)
      - Yerushalmi, Yosef H., 1982-1984 (Box 54, Folder 405)
      - Zelizer, Viviana A., 1979-1983, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 406)
      - Zelizer, Viviana A. - Supplementary Material - Pricing the Priceless Child, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 407)
      - Zucker, Norman L., 1979-1983 (Box 54, Folder 408)
      - Zucker, Norman L. - Supplementary Material - Publications, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 409)
      - Zuckerman, Michael, 1976-1980 (Box 54, Folder 410)
  - Publicity and Publications, 1936-1985; 912; 3 document cases
    - Publications, 1949-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Publications, 1949-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Publications, 1949-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Publications, 1949-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Publications, 1949-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Publications - RF Illustrated - Comments and Requests for Subscriptions, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 0005a)
    - Publications - Reports - Pub-1 - Pub-3, 1936, 1949, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Pub-1: T. B. Appleget; Report on Publicity; December 9, 1936
      Pub-2: Writing Science Papers, Office of Publications, Rockefeller Foundation; 1949
      Pub-3: The Rockefeller Foundation Trustees Bulletin Index 1937-1962; 1962
    - Publications - Reports - Pub-5 - Pub-7, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Pub-5: Trustee Report: Information Service; September 1976
      Pub-6: The Rockefeller Foundation Publishing Program, I. Introduction, II. Objectives, II. Unorthodox Approaches, IV. Ways and Means, V. Staff and Budgets, VI. Appendix I: Letters from RF Illustrated Readers, VII. Appendix II: Roster of Organizations Requesting WORKING PAPERS during October 1977; December 1977
      Pub-7: RF Illustrated Index, Volume 1 thru Volume 3; No Date
    - Publications - Consultants - Beck, Jack, 1965-1979, 1983, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Publications - Consultants - Lear, John, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Publications - Consultants - A-Z, 1965-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Publications - Consultants - A-Z, 1965-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Publications - Consultants - A-Z, 1965-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Publications - Forty Year Review, 1953-1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Publicity, 1949-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Publicity, 1956-1977, 1980, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Publicity, 1956-1977, 1980, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Publicity - Advisor Services, 1949-1962 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Publicity - Consultants - Newsome and Co., 1962-1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Publicity - Consultants - A-Z, 1969-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Publicity - Exhibits, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Publicity - Exhibits, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Publicity - Exhibits, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Service Departments, 1916-1985; 914; 3 document cases
    - Accounting Department, 1916, 1921, 1929, 1935, 1941, 1950, 1954-1956, 1958-1960, 1964, 1967, 1971-1974, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Accounting Department, 1916, 1921, 1929, 1935, 1941, 1950, 1954-1956, 1958-1960, 1964, 1967, 1971-1974, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Accounting Department - Candidates, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Accounting Department - Candidates - A-Z, 1953, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Accounting Department - Reports, 1976, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Filing Department - Fellowships/Scholarships (F/S), 1966-1967, 1969-1975, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records (F.O.R.), 1939, 1942-1944, 1948, 1954-1955, 1959-1963, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records (F.O.R.), 1939, 1942-1944, 1948, 1954-1955, 1959-1963, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Bahia, Brazil, 1972, 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Bahia, Brazil, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      FW notes on file at EED Center
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Bangkok, 1969, 1974-1975, 1977, 1979, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Files - Bangkok, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      FW notes on files at EED Centers
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Cali, 1973-1978, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Guatemala, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Ibadan, 1973-1976, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - India, 1971-1974, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Indonesia, 1972, 1975, 1977-1979, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Indonesia, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      FW notes on files at EFD Center
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Mexico, 1971-1974, 1976-1977, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Philippines, 1969-1970, 1973-1974, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - St. Lucia, 1975-1977, 1974, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Turkey, 1976-1979, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Filing Department - Field Office Records - Zaire, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Office Service, 1920, 1940, 1949-1953, 1955, 1957, 1959-1961, 1963-1966. 1969, 1971-1977, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Purchasing Department, 1949-1969, 1972-1974, 1980, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Purchasing Department, 1949-1969, 1972-1974, 1980, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Purchasing Department - Power of Attorney, 1938, 1948-1949, 1953, 1955, 1958-1959, 1961, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Travel, 1949-1983; 917; 1 document case
    - Travel, 1949-1962, 1964-1969, 1972-1974, 1976-1977, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Travel - Automobiles, 1952, 1954-1956, 1959-1965, 1967-1969, 1972, 1974, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Travel - Certificate of Identity - Proofs and Sample (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, 1953-1977; 923; 10 document cases
    - Documentary Film, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Documentary Film, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Documentary Film, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Documentary Film, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Documentary Film - Requests, 1962-1963, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Documentary Film - Requests - A-L, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Documentary Film - Requests - M-Z, 1961-1966, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Consultants, 1956-1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Consultants - Report of the Commission for the Study of a Livestock Research Program for Colombia, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Consultants - Minutes of the Board of Consultants for Agriculture, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Consultants - Minutes of the Board of Consultants for the Agricultural Sciences, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Consultants - Minutes of the Board of Consultants for the Agricultural Sciences - Vol. I and II, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Consultants - Minutes of the Board of Consultants for the Agricultural Sciences - Vol. I and II, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Consultants - Minutes of the Board of Consultants for the Agricultural Sciences - Vol. III, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Consultants - Agricultural Consultants Meeting, August 10-12, 1964 - Agenda and Background Material (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Consultants - Report and Summary of Agricultural Sciences - Field Directors, Meetings, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Program and Policy, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Program and Policy - Libraries (Agricultural), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Publications, 1958-1963, 1965-1968, 1970, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Publications - History, 1960, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Publications - History, 1960, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, 1955-1959, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Publicity - Reports - Pub-1, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Pub-1: The Agricultural Program of the Rockefeller Foundation; 1956
    - Publicity - Reports - Pub-2, Various Dates (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Pub-2: Journal Series of the RF Agricultural Program, reprints 117-166; Various Dates
    - Publicity - Reports - Pub-2, Various Dates (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Publicity - Reports - Pub-2, Various Dates (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Publicity - Reports - Pub-2, Various Dates (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Staff Information Circulars - Reports - Sic-2 - Sic-5, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Sic-2: Mary Jane Blanton; Division of Natural Science and Agriculture, Staff Information Circular #2, Chile: Land, People and Agriculture; February 1954
      Sic-3: Mary Jane Blanton; Division of Natural Science and Agriculture, Staff Information Circular #3, Peru: Land, People and Agriculture; April 1954
      Sic-4: Central American Corn Breeding Projects, Division of Natural Science and Agriculture (Copy filed RG 3.2 420D Corn Improvement); December 1953
      Sic-5: Division of Natural Science and Agriculture, Staff Information Circular #5, Alaskan Agriculture; August 10, 1954
    - Staff Information Circulars - Reports - Sic-6 - Sic-9, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Sic-6: Mary Jane Blanton; Division of Natural Science and Agriculture, Staff Information Circular #6, Ecuador: Agriculture, Agricultural Education; October 8, 1954
      Sic-7: Mary Jane Blanton; Staff Information, Circular #7 Agriculture in Israel; August 26, 1955
      Sic-8: Mary Jane Blanton; Staff Information, Circular #8 Agriculture in Egypt; August 31, 1955
      Sic-9: Mary Jane Blanton; Staff Information, Circular #9 Edible Oil Crops; January 30, 1956
    - Temporary Aides, 1956-1964 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Temporary Aides, 1956-1964 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Temporary Aides, 1956-1964 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Temporary Aides - Albert, Fritz, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Temporary Aides - Andrews, Frederick N., 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Temporary Aides - Atkins, John G., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Temporary Aides - Bailey, William, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Temporary Aides - Bancroft, T. A., 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Temporary Aides - Beachell, Henry M., 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Temporary Aides - Beachell, Henry M., 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Temporary Aides - Borthwick, H. A., 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Temporary Aides - Bryant, Margaret S., 1960-1964 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Temporary Aides - Butcher, John E., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Temporary Aides - Christensen, Clyde M., 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Temporary Aides - Comstock, Ralph E., 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Temporary Aides - Cooper, A. W., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Temporary Aides - Curry, Norval H., 1955-1957, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Temporary Aides - Cykler, John F., 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Temporary Aides - Dickson, James G., 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Temporary Aides - Dunn, Oliver Charles, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Temporary Aides - Ewing, Elmer E., 1953-1957 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Temporary Aides - Fifield, C. C., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Temporary Aides - Gentry, Robert F., 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Temporary Aides - Gibson, William W., 1956-1960 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Temporary Aides - Grabe, Don F., 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Temporary Aides - Hanna, Gordey C., 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Temporary Aides - Hanson, A. A., 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Temporary Aides - Harvey, Paul H., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Temporary Aides - Hazel, L. N., 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Temporary Aides - Hedrick, Donald W., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Temporary Aides - Hedricks, Sterling B., 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Temporary Aides - Hill, Esther, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Temporary Aides - Hobbs, Charles S., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Temporary Aides - Hutchings, Leslie M., 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Temporary Aides - Jodon, Nelson E., 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Temporary Aides - Kamprath, Eugene J., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Temporary Aides - Kellogg, Charles E., 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Temporary Aides - Knipling, E. F., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Temporary Aides - Kramer, Herbert H., 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Temporary Aides - Krantz, B. A., 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Temporary Aides - Larson, R. E., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 70)